teengrowth.com 2009-06-19

# Teen Growth, the teen resource for advice, health information, social interaction, and fun.

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

TeenGrowth knows your privacy is important and believes your personal information should be kept confidential. To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, TeenGrowth follows to the requirements of the Children Protection and Privacy Act (COPPA) regarding the collection and use of identifiable personal information for children 13 years of age and younger. The following outlines the information gathering and distribution practice on TeenGrowth. 

**Information TeenGrowth Collects**

_Personal Information_  
TeenGrowth does not require that you register personal information such as full names, postal addresses or telephone numbers to access the educational resources on the site. However, TeenGrowth does collect limited information when you access certain areas of the site. These areas include asking medical questions of our Medical Advisory Board (Ask Us) and requesting to receive the weekly newsletter. The information collected is to help us better understand your needs and is never given or sold to third parties. 

Your e-mail address may be used in the "Ask Us" area to contact you directly regarding the question you submitted to our Medical Advisory Board. However, this is only done if you give us permission when you submit the question or if the Advisory Board feels it's in your best interest to contact you, such as in cases of questions related to severe depression or suicide. 

_Non-Personal Information_  
TeenGrowth uses "cookies" to track your activity on the site. This allows us to know which pages you visited, how long you spent on each page, which browser you used to visit the site, the domain name of your Internet provider and how much time you spent on TeenGrowth. The cookies do not identify your personal information such as your name or e-mail address. 

_Surveys_  
From time to time, TeenGrowth may invite you to complete a survey about your likes and dislikes regarding a variety of topics, including products, trends and habits. The purpose of the surveys is to learn about the interests and trends of the teenage market. Any personally identifiable information supplied by you is only for internal use and will not be shared or sold to third parties. 

**Opt-in/Opt-out**  
TeenGrowth uses your e-mail address to send you its weekly newsletter and pertinent updates. We hope you'll agree to let us contact you in this fashion. However, if you prefer not be contacted by TeenGrowth, [click here](http://www.teengrowth.com/index.cfm?action=unsubscribe) and enter your e-mail account in the box provided. You can also send an e-mail to [feedback@teengrowth.com](mailto:feedback@teengrowth.com) and request to be removed from the mailing list. 

**Changing or Deleting Personal Information**  
You may review, update or delete personal information you have supplied to us. You can do this by sending your request to [feedback@teengrowth.com](mailto:feedback@teengrowth.com). If you choose to delete your information, you will no longer be able to receive the newsletter or individual responses that may be sent regarding any questions you submit to our Medical Advisors. However, you will continue to be able to access the education information posted in the general areas of TeenGrowth. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
Throughout the site, TeenGrowth offers links to other sites. When you click on these links, you leave TeenGrowth and our privacy policy no longer applies. Even though TeenGrowth offers links to other sites, it does not imply that TeenGrowth is responsible for or endorses the privacy policies of those sites. 

**Contacting TeenGrowth**  
If you have any questions about TeenGrowth or this privacy statement, you can contact:  
TeenGrowth.com  
11274 W. Hillsborough Ave.  
Tampa, FL 33635
